ceo-worldwide.com 2017-09-09

# Privacy Policy and Disclaimer | CEO Worldwide

## Privacy policy and disclaimer

CEO Worldwide is an executive recruitment agency with focus on international recruitment, interim management, executive search and Management on Demand™. In this very data sensitive business we operate a strict privacy policy. If you have any queries regarding our privacy policy, please contact Janet Clark at [ceo@ceo-worldwide.com](mailto:ceo@ceo-worldwide.com).

* * *

CEO and Founder: Patrick Mataix

Headquarter:  
CEO Worldwide Ltd  
9 Queen‘s Yard – White Post Lane  
London E9 5EN - ENGLAND

Tel: [+44 203 137 2581](tel:+442031372581)  
Email: [ceo@ceo-worldwide.com](mailto:ceo@ceo-worldwide.com)

Company registration number: 8081967

* * *

  1. Privacy
  2. Data collection and purpose specification
  3. Contents of the website
  4. References and links
  5. Copyright
  6. Legal validity
  7. Background checks

* * *

## 1\. CEO Worldwide: Privacy

The submission of all personal or commercial information on the website is purely voluntary. If you supply any personal information (e-mail address, names, postal addresses, CV, etc.) to the CEO Worldwide, we ascertain to collect the information fairly; that is, we inform you if we want to pass the information onto a third party, generally within the international recruitment and _interim management_ process. It will never be supplied to anyone outside the company without first obtaining your consent, unless we are obliged by law to disclose it. Access to your personal data is only possible via a password protected portal, whereby it is your responsibility to keep your personal access codes secret. All pages containing sensitive data are secured through an ssl certificate, this means all data will be encrypted before sending.

You have the right to request a copy of the personal information that CEO Worldwide holds on you and to have any inaccuracies corrected. Please address requests to Mr. Oguidi ([karimo@ceo-worldwide.com](mailto:karimo@ceo-worldwide.com)). We will provide you with a readable copy of the personal data which we keep on you - please note that we require proof of your identity. The provision of this information is free of charge.

You can request to have the data erased, rectified, amended and completed.

* * *

## 2\. CEO Worldwide: Data collection and purpose specification

CEO Worldwide may place a cookie on your computer to collect non-personal statistical information to increase user friendliness on our website. The cookie helps us to collect data on the average time spent viewing a page, common paths taken by visitors through the site, browser settings and other general information. We use this data to improve the services on our site and to refine the user experience.

* * *

## 3\. CEO Worldwide: Contents of the website

CEO Worldwide does not warrant or assume any legal liability or responsibility for the accuracy, completeness or usefulness of any information unless the mistake occurred intentionally or through gross negligence. This refers to any loss, material or immaterial, suffered as a result of the use of this web site. It is explicitly reserved to CEO Worldwide to change, to complement and to delete parts or the entity of this website without prior announcement or to cease its publication temporarily or completely. All offers are subject to change and non-binding.

* * *

## 4\. CEO Worldwide: References and links

We explicitly dissociate from all content of linked sites on our website. This explanation is valid for all external links on this website. Herewith, CEO Worldwide explains explicitly that at the moment of the linking no illegal content appeared on the linked site. The author can not influence the actual and future arrangement, contents or authorship of the linked sites that were changed after linking them. This adoption is valid for all internal links on the own site and for foreign links on the partner-sites.

* * *

## 5\. CEO Worldwide: Copyright

CEO Worldwide aims to respect the copyright of all material published on this website. All mentioned and if applicable otherwise protected trademarks and logos succumb to the particular copyrights. The copyright of all CEO Worldwide owned material lies with CEO Worldwide. CEO Worldwide holds all rights including the rights of reproduction, duplication and distribution (data networks, data carriers).

* * *

## 6\. CEO Worldwide: Legal validity 

This general disclaimer is part of the material offered on the CEO Worldwide website. If any of the terms and conditions should be determined invalid by reason of the relevant laws then the remaining terms and conditions shall remain in full effect.

* * *

## 7\. CEO Worldwide: Background checks

Please note that CEO Worldwide performs background checks on all of our candidates. This solely includes confirmation of previous employment as well as the obtainment of references. No criminal background check is conducted. Therefore, it is strongly recommended that the Client follow up on this process in order to have complete knowledge of the candidate's background, including criminal records and offenses, if any.
